[
    {
        "name": "Walter White",
        "username": "ww.meta@chemistry.org",
        "password": "1234",
        "role": "admin",
        "question": "What was my first pet's name?",
        "answer": "Toto",
        "favourite_warehouse" : "VancouverDC"
    },
    {
        "name": "Mella Galbraeth",
        "username": "mgalbraethe@purevolume.com",
        "password": "1234",
        "role": "associate",
        "question": "What was the last name of my childhood best friend?",
        "answer": "Wick",
        "favourite_warehouse" : "NewWestDC"
    },
    {
        "name": "Salaidh Bagenal",
        "username": "sbagenalm@wunderground.com",
        "password": "1234",
        "role": "associate",
        "question": "What was my favorite subject in school?",
        "answer": "Physical education",
        "favourite_warehouse" : "VancouverDC"
    },
    {
        "name": "Heall Castagne",
        "username": "hcastagne0@foxnews.com",
        "password": "1234",
        "role": "client",
        "question": "Where did I first meet my significant other?",
        "answer": "Vancouver",
        "favourite_warehouse" : "VancouverDC"
    },
    {
        "name": "Yalonda De Normanville",
        "username": "yde2@businesswire.com",
        "password": "1234",
        "role": "client",
        "question": "What was my favorite subject in school?",
        "answer": "Mathematics",
        "favourite_warehouse" : "VancouverDC"
    },
    {
        "name": "Ilise Rosin",
        "username": "irosin3@biglobe.ne.jp",
        "password": "1234",
        "role": "client",
        "question": "What was my first pet's name?",
        "answer": "Fido",
        "favourite_warehouse" : "VancouverDC"
    },
    {
        "name": "Arty Wallsworth",
        "username": "awallsworth6@mtv.com",
        "password": "1234",
        "role": "client",
        "question": "What was my favorite game as a child?",
        "answer": "Truth or Dare",
        "favourite_warehouse" : "VancouverDC"
    },
    {
        "name": "Nona Megarrell",
        "username": "nmegarrell7@taobao.com",
        "password": "1234",
        "role": "client",
        "question": "Who was my most memorable school teacher?",
        "answer": "Ms. Sarah",
        "favourite_warehouse" : "VancouverDC"
    },
    {
        "name": "Jaine Jirik",
        "username": "jjirik8@home.pl",
        "password": "1234",
        "role": "client",
        "question": "What was my favorite toy as a child?",
        "answer": "Videogame",
        "favourite_warehouse" : "VancouverDC"
    },
    {
        "name": "Cecil Hancox",
        "username": "chancox9@google.pl",
        "password": "1234",
        "role": "client",
        "question": "Who was my most memorable school teacher?",
        "answer": "Ms. Paloma",
        "favourite_warehouse" : "VancouverDC"
    }
]